AMIT MANJARLY

Mobile: +91-7359586420 | amitmanjarly9@gmail.com | GitHub: Manjarly | LinkedIn: Amit Manjarly

Objective

A computer engineering graduate and a professional with 2 years of industry experience actively seeking a position as a **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** with an organization in need of a professional with technological skills, multitasking abilities, and drive to exceed corporate objectives.

Professional Experience

Accenture | Associate Software Engineer

March, 2021 - Present

- Currently working as a Quality Assurance for one of the major banks overseas which provided great experience and knowledge in **Banking Domain**.
- Performing Regression, Functional and Manual testing on a daily basis.
- Although from a QA team, I have consistently helped developers to resolve coding errors by looking at bugs while testing the web-application.
- Regularly closing the JIRA stories assigned to me without any spill over in sprint while testing in SIT and UAT environment and helped with Prod testing before the release of epics.

Terminal Trend | Front-End Developer Intern

January, 2021 – February, 2021

- Learned JavaScript while working on various applications.
- Made a web application called Guess The Number which included the use of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Binary Search Algorithm.

Skills and Others

Technical Skills:

• <u>SQL</u> (4 star on HackerRank), JAVA, MySQL, Maven, JDBC, C++, HTML, CSS, Data Structures and Algorithms

OS and Version Control:

• Linux (CISCO - NDG Certified), Windows, Github

Development Methodologies and Tools:

• Agile/Scrum, Kanban, JIRA, Eclipse

Soft Skills:

• Active Listening, Complex Problem Solving, Critical Thinking, Inductive Reasoning, Information Ordering, Mathematical Reasoning, Selective Attention, Speech Clarity

Others:

- Competitive Programming using JAVA on CodeForces (Link: manjarly)
- Data Structures and Algorithms using JAVA on LeetCode (Link: manjarly)
- Uploading self solved solution of CodeForces to GitHub (Link: Manjarly)

Education

L. J. Institute of Engineering and Technology | *Ahmedabad, India* (Gujarat Technological University)

2015 - 2019

• Computer Engineering, Bachelor of Engineering | 8.19 CGPA

Shree Narayana Guru Vidhyalaya | Ahmedabad, India

• 12th – Science | **67.2**%

2014 - 2015

Additional Information

Personally working on:

- Competitve programming mainly on CodeForces, Google CodeJam, Google KickStart and ocassionally on HackerEarth and HackerRank.
- Self learning Data Structures and Algorithms primarily on <u>LeetCode</u> and ocassionally on <u>CodeChef</u>
- YouTube channel where I explain and solve LeetCode questions (Link: <u>Amit Manjarly</u>)
- Learning Linux Kernel, MySQL, JDBC and Hibernate by self using online resources.